sqlines.com 2012-06-08

# Privacy Statement - SQLines

We recognize the importance of protecting your personal information and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. 

SQLines understands that you are concerned about privacy, and we handle your personal information in a safe and responsible manner. 

By accessing or using SQLines.com, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. 

**Collection of Personal Information**

When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as ordering products, SQLines may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. We may require that you provide us with personal information, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and other personal identifying information. 

When ordering products on the site, SQLines has no access to your credit card information. The personal information you submit will remain confidential to SQLines. 

We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We do not share your information with other companies. 

**Use of Cookies**

When you visit SQLines.com, you can surf the site anonymously and access important information without revealing your identity. In order to improve our site, we use “cookies” to track your visit. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. 

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. 

While SQLines.com uses cookies to track your visit to the web site, this information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided us with personal information. 

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, please contact us.
